William Van O'Connor Papers
William Van O'Connor Papers
- Writings
  - Fragments
    - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
Tate, Allen, 1899- 1943 Aug 24 1943 Sep 28 1943 Nov 25 1949 Nov 9 195-Oct 18 1950 Jan 24 1953 Sep 22 1954 Apr 10 1957 Aug 12 1958 Oct 14 1958 Dec 3 1959 Feb 6 1959 Mar 26 1959 Jun 10 1960 Jan 8 1961 Nov 10 1961 Nov 23 1962 Dec 17
Taylor, William E. 1953 advertisement 1954 advertisement 1954 Jan 25 1954 Feb 26 1954 Mar 12 1954 Mar 16 1954 Mar 18 1954 May 21
Thomas Y. Crowell Co. 1959 Jul 9 (Marian F. Hall) 1960 Jan 13 (Robert L. Cromell) 1960 Feb 2 ( " ) 1960 Feb 8 ( " )
Tillyard, Eustace Mandeville Wetenhall, 1889- 1945 May 23
Times Literary Supplement 1954 Jul 27 (Alan Pryce-Jones) 1954 Oct 12
Tindall, William York, 1903- 1949 Mar 22 1951 Jun 21 1959 Sep 6 1961 Apr 24 1963 Mar 24 1964 Jan 12
Tinley, Rene 1966 Nov 22
Tolley, William Pearson, 1900- 1966 Sep 28
Tooker, Stebbin 1966 Oct 14
Trilling, Lionel, 1905- 1947 Feb 23 circa 1948 incomplete 1948 Aug 1 1948 Sep 20 1949 Mar 14 1949 May 27 1949 Jun 14 1949 Sep 27 1949 Oct 10 1949 Oct 18 1949 Oct 20 1950 Mar 7 1954 Oct 20 1956 Mar 7 1956 Nov 9 1957 Aug 14 1958 Feb 18 1959 Jan 6 1959 Jun 11 1959 Nov 16 1960 Jan 4 1960 Dec 11
Troy, William 1948 Sep 19 1948 Sep 25
Unger, Leonard 1962 Nov 1962 Nov 5
University of Chicago Press 1949 Mar 28 (W. T. Couch) 1949 Apr 4 ( " )
Utley, Francis Lee, 1907- 1946 Apr 3 1946 Apr 20 1946 Dec 23
Van Doren, Mark, 1894- 1943 Dec 12 1958 Oct 16
Van Norden, Linda 1962 Jun 6
Varma, D. P. 1965 Mar 9
Viereck, Peter Robert Edwin, 1916- undatedMay 27
Villa, Jose Garcia, 1914- 1946 Apr 16
Virginia Quarterly Review 1956 May 24 (Charlotte Kohler)
Vivas, Eliseo, 1901- 1961 Apr 25 1961 Nov 9
Wain, John Barrington, 1925- 1958 Mar 23 1958 Apr 1 1958 May 13 1958 May 31
Wang, David Rafael 1960 Nov 5
Warnke, Janice 1962 Jul?
Warren, Robert Penn, 1905- undated 1941 Jul 12 1941 Aug 1 (unsigned) 1946 Mar 16 1947 Jul 19 1947 Nov 16 1951 Apr 16 1952 Apr 22 1952 Oct 29 1953 Mar 4 1953 Jun 4 1954 Jun 24 1954 Oct 18 1955 Jul 28 1957 Jul 7 1957 Jul 25 1958 Jan 14 1958 Oct 30 1959 May 2 1961 May 29 1961 Nov 6 1962 Sep 28 1963 Jul 16 1966 Oct 18
Watson, George 1963 Aug 24
Weber, Brom 1963 Apr 7
Weiskopf, F. C. 194-Nov 25
Weiss, Theodore 1944 Jun 17 1944 Sep 19 1945 Aug 26 1945 Sep 30 1946 Apr 24
Wellek, Rene, 1903- 1961 Nov 17
Welty, Eudora, 1909- 1957 Jan 18 1963 Mar 7 telegram
Wentworth, Richard L. see Louisiana State University Press
Wescott, Glenway, 1901- 1963 Jul 22
West, Ray B. 1959 Mar 25
Wheelwright, Philip Ellis, 1901- 1943 Dec 1944 Jan 2
White, Larry see CBS Television Network
Wickes, George 1966 Oct
Wieboldt, John D. see Barnes & Noble, Inc.
Wild, John 1943 Nov 3
Wilder, Amos Niven, 1895- 1949 Jun 20
William Morris Agency 1963 Jan 18 (Helen Strauss)
Williams, Annie Laurie 1963 Sep 30
Williams, Oscar, 1900- 1964 Jul 13
Williams, William Carlos, 1883-1963 1946 May 22 1949 Aug 22
Wilson, Edmund, 1895- 1948 Dec 14
Winsor, Pat 1966 Oct 11
Woolf, Leonard Sidney, 1880- 1954 Aug 14 (Aline Burch, Secy)
Woolman, Marjorie 1966 Oct 27
Yust, Walter see Encyclopaedia Britannica
Zukofsky, Louis 1959 May 29